<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enigma Ladies Salon | Dubai</title>
    <description>An upscale destination in Dubai, UAE offering a complete range of services for the purpose of improving health, beauty and relaxation through personal care treatments. From Manicure &amp; Pedicure stations to a full-fledged Nailbar.
It also has services on hair such as cutting, styling and coloring, a Makeup Section and Spa Services that offer ultra-chic, ultra-comfortable treatment rooms with the finest spa linens and equipment. The Spa offers massages in a variety of styles – traditional Swedish Massage, Deep Tissue work, Hot Stone Massage, Reflexology, Thai etc.
</description>
    <link>https://enigmaladiessalon.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://enigmaladiessalon.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 16:42:47 +0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 16:42:47 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pinktober Specials / Promotions This October</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This Pinktober, let’s participate in raising awareness on every woman’s health. Breast Cancer Awareness month is to honor those who are actively fighting the disease and to help seek a cure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here, we arranged several packages that focuses on your health &amp;amp; well-being&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;book-now--043280033&quot;&gt;Book Now : 043280033&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 14:00:06 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://enigmaladiessalon.com/blog/pinktober-promotions-for-october</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://enigmaladiessalon.com/blog/pinktober-promotions-for-october</guid>
        
        
        <category>promo</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Launching A New Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-new-platform-for-the-latest-news--offers&quot;&gt;A new platform for the latest News &amp;amp; Offers!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, it’s easy to get updated&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 14:00:06 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://enigmaladiessalon.com/blog/new-platform</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://enigmaladiessalon.com/blog/new-platform</guid>
        
        
        <category>nails</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sweet As Candy Colours from Alessandro</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-sweet-colours-of-summer&quot;&gt;The sweet colours of summer!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carefree lightness and pure joie de vivre. You can feel this ultimate summer feeling right to your fingertips. During the hot time of year, the new summer collection SWEET AS CANDY from alessandro International shows how much fun you can have with colour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/img/posts/sweet-as-candy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vivid yellow, bright pink, cool azure. The Candy Colours represent that very special summer feeling. The pure joy of summer and holidays and the colours of these carefree, light days are celebrated wholeheartedly with the current collection SWEET AS CANDY	 from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alessandro-international.com&quot;&gt;alessandro International&lt;/a&gt;. The lively, irresistible candy colours create longing for the sea: the ocean blue &lt;em&gt;Ice Ice Baby&lt;/em&gt; and the mint coloured &lt;em&gt;Pool Party&lt;/em&gt; are the cool, refreshing tones of the collection, while &lt;em&gt;Banana Rama&lt;/em&gt; sets dazzling summer highlights in yellow. The vibrant orange &lt;em&gt;Gummy Bear&lt;/em&gt; and the bright pink &lt;em&gt;Sweet Lollipop&lt;/em&gt; complete this simply delicious summer collection. Yummy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/img/posts/sac-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With SWEET AS CANDY, every sweets lover will find the perfect colour for hot days on the beach and exciting parties. Colourful nails are the most important accessory for your summer look – the best time of year is guaranteed to be sweet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-sweet-as-candy-colours-is-available-in-our-salon&quot;&gt;The SWEET AS CANDY colours is available in our salon!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;about-alessandro-international&quot;&gt;About alessandro International&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Products from alessandro International continue to be synonymous with tradition, quality and innovation. Thanks to its experience of over 25 years, the company is able to offer exceptional know-how and specialist expertise, and these are continuously reflected in its new product ideas and applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a leading system provider, alessandro International offers a complete range of products for the care and appearance of hands, nails and feet. In addition to leading the way in terms of quality and innovation, alessandro International also stands out for the numerous awards it has received and its global distribution network. At the same time, the company and its team of prestigious nail artists have earned the attention of beauty lovers and VIPs worldwide through creative and trend-setting designs and nail looks.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 14:00:06 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://enigmaladiessalon.com/blog/the-sweet-colors-of-candy</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://enigmaladiessalon.com/blog/the-sweet-colors-of-candy</guid>
        
        
        <category>nails</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
